<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ArogyaDhansampda</string>

    <string name="pose1">
		step1:-Stand with your feet together or hip-width apart. Ground down through the four corners of your feet.
		       Roll your shoulders away from your ears, draw your shoulder blades down your back, and lift the crown of your head.\n\n


		step2:-Engage your thighs, draw your belly button in, and lengthen up through the spine. Turn your palms facing the front of the room.
		       Relax your jaw and unforrow your brow. Breathe easy.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose2">  step1:-Start in Mountain Pose. As you inhale, raise your arms, spread your fingers, and reach up through your fingertips. As you exhale,
                                   sit back and down as if sitting into a chair.\n\n


					        step2:-Shift your weight toward the heels and lengthen up through the spine. As you inhale, lift and lengthen through your arms.
		                           As you exhale, sit deeper into the pose.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose3">  step1:-Place your hands on the back of a chair with palms shoulder-distance apart. Step your feet back until they align under hips, creating a right
                                   angle with your body, spine parallel with the floor.\n\n


		                    step2:-Ground through your feet and lift through thighs. Reach hips away from hands to lengthen the sides of your torso. Firm your outer arms in and
					              lengthen through the crown of your head.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose4">  step1:-From all fours, walk your hands 6 inches in front of you. Tuck your toes and lift your hips up and back to lengthen your spine. If your hamstrings
                               are tight, keep your knees bent in order to bring your weight backinto the legs.\n\n
					    step2:-Spread your fingers wide, press into your hands, and rotate your arms so that your biceps are facing toward one another. Press your thighs back
						       toward the wall behind you.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose5">  step1:-Stand with feet wide, 3–4 feet apart. Shift your right heel out so your toes are pointing slightly inward. Turn your left foot out 90 degrees.
                               Line up your left heel with the arch of your right foot.\n\n
					    step2:-Bend your left knee to a 90-degree angle, keeping the knee in line with the second toe to protect the knee joint. Stretch through your straight
					           back leg and ground down into the back foot.\n\n
						step3:-On an inhale, bring arms to a T at shoulder height. Draw your shoulder blades down the back. Spread your fingers and keep palms facedown. Gaze
						       over the front fingers. As you exhale, sink deeper into the stretch.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose6">  step1:-Stand with feet wide, 3–4 feet apart. Shift your right heel out so your toes are pointing slightly inward. Turn your left foot out 90 degrees.
                               Line up your left heel with the arch of your right foot.\n\n
					    step2:-Keeping both legs straight, ground through your feet. Lift arms into a T at shoulder height. Reach forward with your front arm. When you can’t
						       reach anymore, hinge at the front hip.\n\n
						step3:-Bring your front arm down to your shin, a foam block, or the ground. Lift your back arm up toward the sky and spread your fingers. Take your gaze down
  						       to the floor or up toward your lifted hand.\n\n</string>

    <string name="pose7">  step1:-Start in Mountain Pose. Find a fixed point in front of you and stare at it to help you balance.\n\n
					    step2:-As you inhale, shift the weight into your left foot and lift your right foot an inch off the floor. Using your right hand, bring the foot to your
					           shin or inner thigh. Avoid placing your foot directly on the knee.\n\n
                        step3:-As you exhale, ground through the standing leg and lengthen through the crown of your head. Bring your palms to touch in front of your sternum into prayer
       						   hands.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose8">  step1:-Lie faceup with knees bent, feet flat on the floor, and arms at your sides with palms facedown. Keep your feet parallel and hip-width apart,
                               heels stacked under knees.\n\n
					    step2:-On an inhale, activate through the legs and the glutes. Press the floor away with your feet and lift the hips off the floor toward the sky.\n\n

						step3:-If your shoulders are tight and you want more leverage, try holding the sides of your yoga mat and lifting your hips. You may also wish to interlace
       						   your fingers underneath your “bridge” and shimmy your shoulders under the chest.\n\n

						step4:-When you’re ready to come down, lift your heels up and slowly lower your hips back to the ground, one vertebra at a time.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose9">  step1:-Sitting on the floor, bend knees and open them out to the side like a book. Join the soles of your feet together while sitting upright.\n\n
					    step2:-Place fingertips on the floor directly behind you and lengthen up through the spine. You can also hold onto your ankles and hinge forward at
        					   the hips.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose10"> step1:-Sit and straighten your legs out in front of you, grounding your thighs into the floor.\n\n
					    step2:-Hinge at the hips to elongate your torso over your thighs. Grab hold of the outer edges of your feet.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose11"> step1:-Lie faceup, bringing your legs to the outer edges of your mat, like a starfish.\n\n
					    step2:-Splay your feet out to the sides. Place arms along sides, palms facing up. Close your eyes and relax.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose12"> step1:-Start in Downward-Facing Dog. Shift forward so your shoulders are stacked over your wrists. Draw your navel in toward your spine and keep your
                               hips from dropping.\n\n
					    step2:-Reach heels back as you lengthen the crown of your head forward. Ground down into hands, pushing the floor away beneath you. Lengthen
						       through the arms and broaden your chest.\n\n</string>


    <string name="pose13"> step1:-Lie facedown on the floor. Bend elbows and place hands on the mat in line with lower ribs. Hug your elbows in line with your torso. Tuck your
                               toes and take an inhale.\n\n
					    step2:-As you exhale, push the floor away like a push-up. Straighten your arms and broaden across the chest, hovering your hips a few inches above the floor at
						       the same time.\n\n
	</string>


    <string-array name="title_story">
        <item>for thin body</item>
        <item>for fat body</item>
        <item>for avarege body</item>
        <item>for old people</item>
        <item>for child(8to15)</item>
        <item>to eat in morning</item>
        <item>water cossumption</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="details_story">
        <item>for thin body:- sfnshjfnknfdklsafjbgfndjfkngerkfdnkvfjeponvhasofinfhdsla</item>
        <item>for fat body:- jo kanr ahai karo mera man ko jskfjsomf jftusnfdshmldjs'pfo</item>
        <item>for avarege body:- fkjaf;hspfimds,ijsr08u[m,[fpkm,-fiofjmue</item>
        <item>nsdklopkllmdsk[f0im[plf[pis-0dfk[k</item>
        <item>.fdki9kmfdkpdkfieof-</item>
        <item>f,mpdojj0e9uf0j</item>
        <item>ldfjpwuf08u8f0uw-0</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="ArogyaDhansampda">
        <item>Nutrition Guide</item>
        <item>healthy food to eat</item>
        <item>beginner to advanced</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>